(objects clattering)
(device whirring)
Mm-mmm.
(zips bag)
(trilling)
You're alive.
(machines whirring)
(monitor beeping)
What are you dreaming,
little angel?
(sniffs)
(yawns)
(gasps)
(grunts)
(beeps)
(gasps)
Well...
Try again.
Well, that's the best
I can do for now.
CYBORG:
I'm really grateful, Doc.
I'll be getting some overtime
next week.
Yeah, pay me when you can.
CYBORG: Here,
I got these for you.
My wife works out
at Farm 22.
(chuckles) Thank you.
CYBORG: See you next time.
Keep getting paid in fruit,
and we'll be picking
these ourselves.
Hello, sleepyhead.
Hi.
How do you feel?
Okay.
Any pain anywhere?
No.
Numbness?
Motor dysfunction?
I'm a little hungry.
IDO: Eat this.
Get your sugar levels up.
(laughs)
Taste receptors are working.
Thank you.
You'll like this a whole lot
better with the peel off.
I don't mean to be rude...
but am I supposed
to know you?
Actually...
we haven't met.
I'm Dr. Dyson Ido.
This is Nurse Gerhad.
And do you know who I am?
Well, we were hoping...
you'd fill in that part.
Since you're
a total replacement cyborg...
and most of your cyber body
was destroyed...
we can't find any records.
But your very human brain
was miraculously intact.
Theoretically, you should
remember something.
Oh. Well...
It's still pretty blank.
No, it's completely blank,
actually.
I don't even
know my own name.
Let's look at the bright side.
Your tears are working.
Mmm.
That's so good.
What do you call this?
(indistinct chatter)
Yeow! What's that?
Zalem.
Oh!
The last of
the great sky cities.
What holds it up? Magic?
No.
Something stronger.
Engineering.
(man shouts in Spanish)
And down here,
we have Iron City.
With all its charm.
Dr. Dyson Ido. That's you.
While I'm learning names,
do you have one for me?
Alita.
It's a nice name.
I love it.
Can I keep it?
At least until I can
remember my real name?
IDO: Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Okay.
Do you want to take a look?
Yes.
(people shouting
in multiple languages)
Why are there
so many languages?
Um, after the big war
I told you about...
ALITA: The Fall.
After The Fall,
only Zalem was left...
and survivors came here
from all over the world.
Everybody down here
works for Zalem.
The Factory, the Farms...
Does anyone ever
go up to Zalem?
(gasps) We should go.
Nobody from down here
ever goes up.
It's a rule
that's never broken.
What?
ANNOUNCER: Oh!
And he takes him down hard!
What is that?
IDO: It's Motorball.
That's so cool.
Nothing you need to be
wasting your time watching.
(playing modern
classical music)
(coin clatters)
Alita.
One minute, please.
(dog whimpers)
Hi.
Hello.
You want some?
Here you go.
Can I hug you?
Hi.
(giggles)
CENTURION: Step aside.
Out of the way.
(both grunt)
(dog barks)
(dog yelping)
Outstanding.
Why don't you watch
where you're going?
I gotta admit...
I never saw anybody
challenge a Centurion before.
Whoa. You're heavy.
I mean...
Oh.
You're a cyborg.
Sorry, I was just
admiring your hand.
Can I see?
Wow.
It's really nice work.
Did Doc Ido do it?
He built all of me.
Except my core. That's mine.
Well, he did
a really great job.
Hey, what are those things?
The Centurions?
(chuckles)
What planet are you from?
Ido found me
in the Scrapyard.
The Scrapyard?
Mm-hmm.
But that would mean...
Hey, Doc.
I got those driver-boards
you were looking for.
Alita is new here.
She's still learning
about things.
HUGO: I gotta go.
I'll drop those off later.
I need a rebuild
on a quad servo.
Maybe I'll see you around.
Who is that?
IDO: Hugo.
He's a hard worker, but...
Alita, come on,
let's go home.
(engine starts)
Hugo.
Let's go home.
(keys jangling)
(metal thuds)
(gasps)
(meows)
(weapon unsheathes)
(screams)
There's the damn Jackers
that ripped me to shreds
standing right there.
And that vale madre Centurion
wouldn't lift a finger.
Why would anyone wanna
take your arms and legs?
Torque coupling.
Those Jackers want your parts
for the black market.
To supply the Motorball games.
You were lucky.
Another girl was murdered
last night, right near there.
Yeah, I heard that guy
carves girls up...
and sells their body parts.
(shushes)
CYBORG: Sorry, Doc.
For now, I don't want you
out after dark.
Is that understood?
Okay.
And if you go out
during the day,
don't wander too far
from this neighborhood.
Okay.
Promise?
I promise.
Hey, kid.
Hey, what's your problem?
Who's the girl?
My new assistant.
I was surprised to see her
in our daughter's body.
You were supposed to have
destroyed that years ago.
I couldn't.
Clearly.
And did you tell her
who you built that body for?
(sighs)
Our daughter is dead, Chiren.
You need to let it go.
Oh.
It's obviously not me that's
clinging to something here.
(indistinct chatter)
(indistinct shouting)
PLAYER: Over here!
(players cheering)
Hugo.
Hey, Alita.
Is this Motorball?
It's just a scrimmage.
Do you wanna join in?
(chuckles)
Come on, every kid's
gotta play Motorball.
Sure, why not?
I want us
to be a team again.
I have a great new setup...
and equipment...
worthy of your skills.
Together, we can build
the finest champions
this game has ever seen.
Could be my ticket home.
When are you going to realize
there is no way back?
It just does not happen.
Vector can make it happen.
I can't believe
you trust Vector.
He has very high connections.
I won't help you
build monsters.
I'm going to get back
to Zalem somehow.
I'll claw my way there with
my bare hands if I have to.
Hey, everyone,
this is Alita.
Hi.
Best way to learn
is to go in.
PLAYER 1: Pass the ball!
HUGO: That's it.
Lean into your turns,
look for an opening.
I think I'm getting it!
(crowd exclaims)
HUGO: You can let go
of the remote now.
Oh, crap.
(indistinct shouting)
PLAYER 2: Come on, get her!
PLAYER 3: Come on, get her!
PLAYER 2: Cut her off!
Koyomi, pass her the ball.
And she got it! She got it!
PLAYER 4: Get her!
(crowd exclaims)
Sorry, princess.
Nice, Tanji, thanks.
She's never played before.
(players cheering)
Sorry.
(cheering)
Got this!
Mine!
PLAYER 5: You got me!
(screams)
(crowd exclaims)
(cheering and whooping)
KOYOMI: Good shot.
Your freak girlfriend's got
some serious malfunctions.
I'm really sorry.
She humiliated you
so severely.
(laughs sarcastically)
All right,
I'll see you tonight.
And, uh,
she's not my girlfriend.
Whatever.
(Hugo grunts)
You've got some talent
for this game.
I've got to get home now.
Ido wants me in the house
before dark.
Do you want a ride?
(laughing)
So you can't
remember anything?
I'm trying to.
Family, friends,
favorite food?
Nothing. Well, maybe oranges.
But that's just
since yesterday.
Oranges?
Uh-huh.
Nope. Unacceptable.
Here, check this out.
Thank you very much, Senora.
SALESMAN: And here you go.
Thank you.
You ready?
Try this.
Trust me.
It's chocolate.
Mmm.
That is so great.
It's good, right?
I have a favorite food now.
(laughs)
HUGO: Thank you.
This is my favorite food.
Well, I wouldn't
call it that.
I would.
Hey, look. Check it out.
It's a Hunter-Warrior.
He's a bounty hunter.
Named Zapan.
Scanning for his mark.
I wouldn't wanna be that guy.
ALITA: Look at that sword.
All guns are outlawed
in Iron City.
Punishable by death.
Anything that
challenges Zalem.
(gate squeaking)
Didn't I tell you to be home
before dark?
What's the big deal?
I just lost track of time.
Yeah. Don't trust anyone.
People do terrible things
to each other here.
What happened to your arm?
Here, eat this.
You okay?
You still need proper
nourishment for your brain.
You have any chocolate?
HUGO: It's a harsh world.
The strong prey
on the weak down here.
You gotta stay focused
on your dream.
What's your dream?
I'll show you.
This is my secret place.
Best view in town.
Wow.
Really cool.
(chuckles) No. Look.
That view.
ALITA: Oh.
Right.
I wonder
what it's like up there.
HUGO: Better than this dump
down here.
Listen.
(machinery humming
in distance)
It's stuff from the Factory
going up to Zalem.
But the tubes are just
for cargo, not for people.
If I was as strong as you,
I'd climb that tube
to Zalem right now.
They don't let anybody
up there.
Yeah, that's what they
want you to think.
You just gotta know
the right people.
I happen to be connected.
Oh.
You gotta be willing
to do what it takes.
Whatever it takes.
Funny thing is,
you've seen it.
You just can't remember.
What do you mean?
Doc found you
in the Scrapyard.
All that stuff is dumped
from Zalem.
So you must be from up there.
I guess so.
If you could just tell me
what those eyes have seen.
I wish I could.
I keep trying to
remember, but...
It's still a blank.
I'm starting to feel
like I wasn't very important.
Just an insignificant girl
thrown out with
the rest of the garbage.
(Hugo sighs)
(door closes)
No! Stop!
Alita!
Don't do it!
IDO: Oh, no.
It's a trap.
Looking for me, Doctor?
Or should I say,
Hunter-Warrior? (chuckles)
"Hunter-Warrior"?
(cackling)
ROMO: Oh, no.
Looks like he's got us.
IDO: Don't move.
Hey, thanks for
bringing a girl.
That's gonna save us
some time.
(yells)
(Romo laughing)
Nice shot, for a Meat-Boy.
(grunts)
No!
NYSSIANA:
You came to rescue me?
That is so sweet.
(chuckles)
You have nice eyes.
He's mine.
You can have the girl.
So long as I get his eyes.
Alita, run!
(grunts)
(grunting)
My God.
Rip that flea!
NYSSIANA:
You are so beautiful.
I wanna rip you open
and see if you're ugly inside.
Like the others.
(both grunting)
Watch her die.
(snarls)
(grunting)
(grunts)
Come here, little flea...
so I can pinch
your head off.
(grunting)
Hi-yah!
GELDA: 99!
On your left!
Hi-yah!
(roars)
(groans)
(grunts)
You'll pay, little flea.
Grewishka does not forget.
I'm coming for you.
Both.
(laughs)
(panting)
GREWISHKA:
Grewishka does not forget!
ALITA: When I was fighting,
I remembered something.
I was in a huge battle.
IDO: You surprised me.
ALITA: Well,
you surprised me, too.
Before The Fall...
there were police
to stop criminals.
Now, the Factory pays us
to do the dirty work.
Hunter-Warrior 17739.
You are a Hunter-Warrior.
(door chimes)
You stay here.
Don't kill anyone.
Bounty for the cyborg Nyssiana
was 20,000 credits.
(metallic rattling)
You should've told me
who you really are.
And do you do it
for the money?
I take the money.
Otherwise the clinic
would've closed long ago.
I do this work
for other reasons
I'd rather not talk about.
You have to talk about it.
Something during the fight
triggered a memory.
I was on the moon.
You know more about me
than you're saying.
Whose body is this?
Who am I?
ALITA: This was your daughter?
You built this body for her?
Her name was Alita.
She was really looking forward
to waking up
with legs that could run.
You built her
a pair of fast legs.
She never got to use them.
She was murdered.
What happened?
A patient of mine
came to the clinic one night,
looking for drugs.
I was a tuner
for the Motorball games...
and I had made a machine body
for him of obscene strength.
He was my demon,
coming back to me.
Hey! What are you doing there?
(grunts)
(screams)
(grunting)
Alita couldn't get out
of the way fast enough.
Her mother, Chiren,
couldn't deal with
Alita's death.
Maybe she just
couldn't deal with me.
So I went hunting.
I needed to kill him.
Maybe I was just hoping
that he would kill me.
It brought no peace.
There were other demons
like him out there...
and I felt, somehow, I was
responsible for all of them.
So I registered
as a Hunter-Warrior.
There's nothing noble
about it.
Did you ever find peace?
I found you.
I'm not your daughter.
I don't know what I am.
I do.
Have a look
at your original Cyber-core.
(typing)
This is your brain.
A normal healthy
teenage girl's brain.
If there is such a thing.
But this is your heart.
Part of your original core...
powered by
an Anti-Matter Micro-Reactor.
So I've got a strong heart?
(chuckles)
You have a heart
strong enough
to power all of Iron City
for years.
This is lost technology.
Nobody's made
this stuff since...
before The Fall.
(chuckles) Yeah, right.
So I'm 300 years old?
Sweetheart, you are.
I don't want my players losing
unless I tell them to.
It can't be left to chance.
You promised me champions.
And you promised me
the best of everything.
Get those military servos
I asked for.
You don't have
a winning attitude.
Just be ready
for tomorrow's game.
(muffled thumping)
(Grewishka groaning)
GREWISHKA: Help me.
CHIREN: Grewishka?
Why should I waste
my talent on you?
Look what she's done to me.
Ido's little cyber girl.
What did you say?
ALITA: The woman in my memory
called me 99.
IDO: What you saw was a flash
of your previous life.
ALITA: Who was I?
IDO: In time, you'll remember.
(exhales deeply)
(machine trilling)
(machine whirring)
(groaning)
I wanna rip her in half.
VECTOR: Grewishka.
Oh, how the mighty
have fallen.
Are we stripping him
for parts?
I need you to
look at something.
It's a Telepresence Chip.
He's wired.
Somebody in Zalem
is riding him.
There are watchers behind
the eyes all over the city.
Pretty common now.
I'd just as soon remove it...
while I'm rebuilding him.
VECTOR:
Why are you wasting time
on this burnt-out
street junk?
CHIREN:
It's a personal matter.
GREWISHKA: (in different tone)
Do you like your job, Vector?
If you like your position
and the many comforts
that come with it...
I strongly suggest
you listen to Dr. Chiren.
Nova.
My apologies.
Who did this to Grewishka?
A little cyborg girl.
Though the impact points
are evidence
of extraordinary power...
I don't understand
how she could create
such force
with such a small body.
It was not the power
of the body that did this.
It was the mind.
She knows the fighting
techniques of Panzer Kunst.
Rebuild Grewishka.
Have him bring her to me.
Dead.
(strained grunting)
He's gone.
(distorted) Not gone.
(gasps)
Repatched.
You're a clever woman, Doctor.
And determined to reach
your goal at any cost.
So I'll make you this offer.
If and when
you have pleased me...
I will grant you
the destiny you seek.
Zalem.
You'll send me to Zalem?
I'm there right now.
Consider my services engaged.
(grunts)
(groans)
There is no bounty
on Grewishka.
But you reported it
to the Factory.
Him killing
all of those women...
Somebody's protecting him.
Who has the power to do that?
Someone far beyond us here.
We better stay off
the street for now.
I wanna be
a Hunter-Warrior like you.
Alita, that's impossible.
We could be a team.
Alita, this is dangerous,
dirty work.
I know.
No, you don't.
How is that
your choice to make?
It's out of the question.
I might need
a life-or-death situation
to remember who I was.
Even if it's just
for a second.
Alita, some things are
better left forgotten.
I don't want blood
on these hands, too.
Then I'll find out
for myself.
Alita.
(cheering)
ALITA: I'm just tired of it.
He just wants me
to be his perfect little girl.
HUGO: So, you gonna live
by his rules or yours?
ANNOUNCER: What a battle!
These two have been going
at each other all match.
Welcome to Motorball.
(cheering)
ANNOUNCER:
Jashugan has got the ball.
Claymore attacks!
Jashugan takes him out!
Masakus sends Jashugan flying!
Kutty now with the ball,
one point.
Zariki is in hot pursuit.
(engine revs)
Wipeout, Zariki!
Whoo!
And he throws Kutty
like a rag doll!
Come on.
Let me show you something.
I know all the pit crews
and tuners.
I'll introduce you around.
Who's the top player?
Right now, I'd say Jashugan
has the best chance
of making Final Champion.
Camber's still off
in the left bogie.
I was oversteering
in turn six.
What's Final Champion?
It's the best thing
a Motorball player can win.
Every few years,
they choose a player
that can't be beaten...
and he gets to go to Zalem.
PLAYER: Hey, Hugo.
JASHUGAN: Slow is smooth,
smooth is fast.
Do it once, do it right.
Juggernaut needs to pit,
right now.
Do you like to lose?
Then get him in here.
Claymore is a rebuild.
Why is he not tracking?
CHIREN: Alita's here.
That's Vector.
He basically runs Motorball.
We do a lot of business
with his team.
Selling parts to him
and his new tuner.
Chiren.
Let's go, guys. Come on,
get me back out there.
What? You're not the only one
with connections.
ANNOUNCER: Kutty closing in
on Juggernaut.
Kinuba has Kutty
in his sights.
(screams)
(yelling)
Oh! Kinuba went through him
like laundry
with those Grindcutters.
Is that weapon even legal?
Kinuba's too strong
with that new weapon.
He's screwing up the odds.
You know...
I could really use
his Grindcutters...
for our other project.
ANNOUNCER: Crimson Wind making
her way through the field.
So, what do you think?
(crowd exclaiming)
I like it.
Yo, Hugo. We gotta go.
Hey, something's come up.
Where are you going?
I just gotta do something.
Can you get back okay?
Yeah, sure.
Can you go out tomorrow?
I wanna show you this place
me and Tanji know.
It's out in the Badlands.
It might help
with your memory.
I'd appreciate that.
Thanks.
For everything.
ANNOUNCER: Wow!
He is throwing down!
(laughing)
Whoo!
Oh, shit!
What the hell?
Shit.
(grunts)
(yells)
(groaning)
MAN: Hurry up!
You're dead!
You little runts!
I'm gonna smash your skulls!
(grunting)
KINUBA:
You can't do this to me!
MAN1: Ready.
MAN2: Give me.
(groans)
Careful.
KINUBA: You street punks!
I'm gonna
make you pay for this.
Nice work.
Compliments to your crew.
Thank you, sir.
I'll pass it on.
Hey, man, where's my cut?
Hey, when you gonna tell
your hardbody
you jack cyborgs, huh?
I'm not.
And neither are you.
You afraid
she's gonna cut you loose?
(grunts)
Get the Grindcutters
over to Chiren right away.
Use the service gate.
Go.
(panting)
KINUBA: Vector, you prick.
I should've known.
What you should've known,
my friend...
is that no one...
is greater than the game.
(screams)
ALITA:
What's outside the city?
HUGO: Not much.
The war
wiped out all utilities
and most everything else.
All we know is the sky cities
fell all in one night...
when the enemy launched
the last attack
with every ship they had.
Who was the enemy?
The URM.
United Republics of Mars.
The U-R-M.
ALITA: URM.
On that last night
of the war...
the earth shook
and the sky burned.
But in the morning,
Zalem still stood.
It's just up ahead.
This ship is from
the battle of Zalem.
I figured that
maybe seeing stuff
from the war would
help trigger your...
Salvagers have jacked
some stuff
over the years for metal...
but it's all URM technology,
so it's mostly been
left alone.
This is an URM ship?
HUGO: Uh-huh.
You know, it's pretty hard
to sell this stuff
since no one knows
what it is...
Shh!
We have to go
to the command deck.
It's forward.
How does she know that?
Hey, we can't get there.
It's underwater.
How long do you think
she can hold her breath?
I don't know.
(exhales deeply)
(beeping)
(clangs)
(breathes deeply)
Oh, this can't be good.
(machine trilling)
(sighs)
Forget it.
I won't do it.
But...
But you have to.
This would help us
fight Grewishka
and anyone else
he sends after us.
This body...
it has the power I need.
I feel a connection to it
I can't explain.
This could be who I am.
You've been given
a chance to start over,
with a clean slate.
How many of us get that?
Why did an enemy warship...
respond to me?
Because I knew that ship.
I've been on others like it,
haven't I?
Haven't I?
Ouf, whatever you were,
it's not who you are now.
No!
I'm a warrior, aren't I?
And you know.
You've always known.
This is called a Berserker.
It's a humanoid weapon-system
created by the URM Technarchy.
Your core
was designed to interface
with this type of body.
Your identity code
activated it.
The instinctive
fighting technique you use...
is Panzer Kunst,
a lost combat art
for machine bodies.
It was used
by the Berserkers.
This is why you're drawn to
conflict without hesitation.
It's part of your training.
You are not just
a warrior, Alita.
You're an URM Berserker,
the most advanced
cyborg weapon ever created.
And that is exactly why
I will never unite you
with this body.
That's fine.
Fine.
(sighs)
State your business.
I'm here to register
as a Hunter-Warrior.
How'd it go?
You're a Hunter-Warrior,
all right.
Doc's gonna be pissed.
Whose rules do I live by?
(indistinct chatter)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are you sure about this?
This place is just for
bounty hunters, nobody else...
What do you think this is?
Besides, Ido says
I'm drawn to conflict.
(whimpers)
Oh. I remember you.
How's it going, little guy?
Good? (giggles)
Just watch my back.
Oh, boy.
(rock music playing)
(indistinct shouting)
BARKEEP: Hey, Zapan!
Not the furniture.
What brings you
in here, sweets?
Come to see the Hunters
up close?
Not exactly.
(chuckles)
Cupcake here is
a bounty hunter.
What?
(laughter)
So, you went down,
you filled out
your application forms...
you got your ID badge...
and now you're just
like us, yeah?
Let me introduce you
to some of your
professional colleagues.
This is Master Clive Lee
of the White Hot Palm.
He has over
200 confirmed kills.
207.
ZAPAN:
Well, and this is Screwhead,
one of our most lethal
bounty hunters.
And then, there's McTeague...
the Dogmaster,
with his Hellhounds.
(Hellhound growls)
His biggest problem is having
enough left to identify after,
so he can collect the bounty.
(Hellhounds growling)
(dog whimpers)
And then, there's me.
Zapan.
Keeper of the legendary
Damascus Blade.
Honed to a monomolecular edge.
It slices armor like butter.
Forged before The Fall
by the lost arts
of URM metallurgy.
And who did you kill
to acquire it?
(sighs)
(sword sheathes)
A Hunter-Warrior
is a solitary predator.
You'll be competing against us
for the kill.
You can see
what you're up against.
Thanks.
I came to ask
for your help...
against our common enemy,
Grewishka.
He's being protected
by the system,
and continues
to rampage unchecked.
And now,
he's after Ido and me.
So I'm calling on you...
my Hunter-Warrior brothers.
Let's band together
and defeat him
once and for all.
(snickering)
(Hunter-Warriors laughing)
Any takers? Hmm?
No?
Big surprise.
You know, normally,
I wouldn't take a rookie
under my wing...
share my knowledge.
I'm willing to make
an exception in your case...
if you'll cut loose
Meat-Boy over here
and let me buy you a drink.
Hey, watch it.
And what could I learn
from a loudmouth pretty boy...
who spends all of his money
on his face?
(laughter and whistling)
Maybe I'll pull
your arms and legs off,
roll your head around
in the street.
Maybe that'll teach you
some manners.
(laughs)
You might mess up your hair.
(exclaiming and laughing)
HUNTER-WARRIOR 1:
You gonna take that, Zapan?
HUNTER-WARRIOR 2: He's scared
of the pretty girl.
Aah!
(crowd exclaims)
(grunts)
You do not deserve
such a weapon.
I heard you were
the heroes of Iron City.
I am not impressed.
What the hell are you doing?
(whispers) I'm gonna need you
to stand way back.
I will take on anyone
in this room.
And if I win...
you fight alongside me.
This bitch broke my nose.
Yes, I did.
Heroes?
All I see are junkyard punks,
assorted cyber-trash...
and a bunch of drunken
Motorball burnouts
too slow to play the game.
(all grunting)
(device crackling)
Thanks, Hugo.
(yelling)
Oh, no.
Hold it!
Knock it off!
Or no more free repairs!
I'm with her.
Sorry about this.
You and I are going
to have a little talk.
No, we had our talk.
You didn't leave me
another choice.
(all grunting)
IDO: Don't move.
It's Grewishka.
What's happened to him?
Well, to answer
your question...
I've had a little upgrade.
I'm only here for the girl.
Ah, she's all yours.
What about the rest of you?
There ain't no bounty
on this guy, Doc.
(chuckles)
Not our problem.
It's all right, Ido.
(dog yaps)
(growls, barking)
Aw.
The only one with courage.
So innocent.
(extracts weapon)
(barking stops)
(all exclaiming)
(grunts)
Iron City is no place
for innocents, little flea.
ALITA: I do not stand by
in the presence of evil.
I do not stand by
(breathing heavily)
Come to my world.
(Grewishka laughs)
Come, little flea.
Alita! No!
(Grewishka laughs)
GREWISHKA: Welcome to
the underworld. My world.
From here, there are worlds
above worlds above worlds...
going farther up
than you can imagine.
And the trash of each one
flows down to the one below...
'til it all ends up here.
It's where I used to live.
And it's where
you're going to die.
(grunting)
(crackling)
(scoffs)
Dance, little flea.
(groaning)
(grunts)
I was forgotten here to rot.
But I was saved...
remade...
by the same hand that
shapes your destiny even now.
Whose hand?
My master, Nova.
What do you know about me?
(Alita yelling)
(yells)
(weapons sheathe)
GELDA: You have the soul
of a survivor.
(grunting)
You'll never give up.
Aah.
Know what is hidden.
Always ask...
what is it that
you are not seeing?
ALITA: Nova?
GELDA: He is the dragon
that must be slain.
Again.
GREWISHKA: Look at you.
(grunts)
Where are you going?
(grunting)
What's the matter?
My little toy doesn't
want to play anymore?
(grunts)
I'll turn you
into a living pendant
to adorn my chest.
Then I can hear your voice
every moment of the day...
pleading for mercy!
(grunting)
(Grewishka chuckling)
Hi-yah!
(Grewishka screams)
(grunts)
Fuck your mercy.
(groaning)
No!
(growling)
(panting and groaning)
(Hellhounds barking)
Break off!
(barking)
He wasn't a dog lover.
I hate that.
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You think you can replace us
that easily?
Bring her back
as many times as you like.
No one will dare
harm you again.
(machine trilling)
It's the adaptive technology
of the Berserker body.
The shell is reconfiguring
to her subconscious image
of herself.
I've never seen
anything like it.
It's making micro-adjustments
throughout every system.
Looks like she's a little
older than you thought.
Well, look at you.
Well, you were right.
A warrior's spirit needs
a warrior's body.
(whooshing)
It draws in air,
generating an arc plasma...
but how you control it,
I don't know.
Didn't exactly
come with a manual, did you?
It's some kind of weapon.
Now you know who you are.
But that's just a shell.
It's not bad or good.
That part's up to you.
Check these out.
Pretty fresh, right?
Alita!
Wow.
You're...
Back together?
Very back together.
(chuckles)
You look...
different.
It's all nanotech.
It's a bunch of stuff even
Ido hasn't figured out yet.
So are you stronger
than you were?
Yeah. And faster, too.
It feels...
more me.
HUGO: You know,
some guys might be
intimidated by
a girl like you.
ALITA: Really? Why is that?
'Cause you could
rip my arm off
and beat me
with the wet end.
(both laugh)
Well, then,
don't piss me off.
Why don't you like her?
I just never got
the whole hardbody thing.
And besides, she's URM.
It means she was probably
the enemy at one point.
Yeah, 300 years ago.
Get over it.
(chuckles)
I'm a lot more
touch sensitive, too.
A lot higher density
of force feedback and...
texture sensors.
You wanna try it?
You can feel this?
Yes.
Close your eyes.
How about this?
Yes.
Where am I now?
You're...
with me.
Does it bother you...
that I'm not completely human?
You are the most human person
I have ever met.
(Grewishka grunting)
(objects clattering)
He won't even let me
fix his eye.
He says he wants the pain.
Enough.
(grunts)
Nova.
You have failed me.
Stand.
You will never triumph until
you understand what she is.
She's the last of her kind.
The finest weapon
of the URM Technarchy.
I need you to destroy
this Alita.
I need you to bring me
her heart.
I live only for her death.
VECTOR: I hate
when he does that.
This is not a man
who tolerates failure.
I'm not trusting my future
to a piece of iron.
What do you have in mind?
To dreams.
I like your drive, Hugo.
You have a solid future
with my team.
My future's in Zalem.
I remember your promise
every day.
To send me up.
When I get you
a million credits.
Personally...
I'd rather rule in hell
than serve in heaven.
We'd be at the bottom
of the food chain up there,
but down here...
we can live like kings.
So...
Tell me about
this friend of yours.
Alita?
Is that her name?
Alita. Hmm.
Hi.
(groans)
What happened to you?
I wound up hanging out
with Vector.
Some alcohol was involved.
Apparently.
So, Vector?
Is that your connection
for getting into Zalem?
Yeah.
Oh.
I was hoping maybe
you'd wanna stay.
Hey, it's not right away.
I still gotta raise
the rest of the money first.
It's okay.
It's your dream.
I know it's what
you've always wanted.
You know...
I was always so sure.
Now you come along...
nothing's clear anymore.
How much more do you need
before you can go?
90k.
90k?
I can make that in bounties.
I'll just figure out who has
the highest prices
on their heads...
and then I'll take them out.
No, I can't ask you
to do that for me.
I'd do whatever
I had to for you.
I'd give you whatever I have.
What are you doing?
(heart beating)
I'd give you my heart.
Take it.
It's got an URM Micro-Reactor
for a power supply,
probably worth millions.
With your connections,
you can find a buyer...
you could make enough for
both of us to go to Zalem...
and then we just find
a cheap replacement...
No.
Come on, you buy
and sell parts all day long.
Don't just do things
for people.
No matter how good
you think they are,
or how deserving they are.
It's all or nothing with me.
This is who I am.
I know.
It's okay.
Put it back.
(Alita sighs)
(puffs)
That was pretty intense, huh?
(chuckles)
Yeah, that was very intense.
(laughs)
Sorry.
Maybe there's another way.
Vector wants you to try out
for Second League.
What?
You become
a big Motorball star,
make a pile of money...
we can go to Zalem together.
What are you talking about?
I can't be
a pro Motorball player.
Ali...
you could be a champion.
You win this tryout...
every scout will be killing
each other to get to you.
We'll be home free.
Only if you'll be my coach.
Well, if that's what it takes.
(chuckles)
That's what it takes.
Are you going to kill her?
No.
Much worse.
(scoffs)
(muffled crowd cheering)
Ido, can a human love
a cyborg?
Why?
Does this cyborg
love a human?
Mm-hmm.
A human can love a cyborg...
but you have to keep your mind
on the game, Alita.
It can get very rough
out there.
Even for a tryout.
Try these.
Did you make these for me?
Yes.
They won't make you
any faster. It's regulation.
But at least
they won't fail you.
Here's our deal.
You go in there, you race,
you win,
you come back right here.
You wear all of these pads,
especially this one.
(Gerhad laughs)
I don't need all this crap.
Yes, you do.
Remember...
if you wreck this body,
I can't fix it.
This is URM technology.
Yes, I know.
Now, go find
a place to watch,
because you're
making me nervous.
(Gerhad chuckles)
Good luck.
Bye.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
You are the scum of the game.
But tonight,
you are handpicked scum.
Because tonight is not a game.
It is a hunt.
I'm paying 500,000...
to the one who kills
the girl called Alita.
(comm chimes)
Hey.
Where are you?
The tryout's about to start.
I'm on my way.
There's something
I've gotta do first.
I'm doing this for us,
remember?
You can't miss it.
I won't. Trust me.
Please, just stop.
I didn't do anything to you.
TANJI: It's just business.
Nothing personal.
Tanji, stop!
TANJI: Using my name?
Man, what's wrong with you?
I can't do this anymore.
What's the matter? You're
already gone half the time.
Now you show up
with this line of crap!
It's the little hardbody,
isn't it?
Listen, it's over.
Do you understand?
I'm out.
And if you had any brains,
you'd leave this behind, too.
I'm out.
For good.
You should've jacked that
bitch when you had the chance.
Would've been on your way
to Zalem right now.
(grunting)
(laughing)
Well, very professional.
Hey, man,
we don't want any trouble.
If this is your mark,
we're sorry. He's all yours.
(sighs)
Hugo.
Jacking cyborgs.
Your little girlfriend
might take that
kind of personally,
don't you think?
Hmm?
But you know girls.
She'll probably get all weepy
and forgive you...
when I show her your head.
There's no marker out on me.
There will be.
Murder pulls
a tight little bounty...
even with gutter trash
like you.
I never killed anyone.
You just did.
(grunts)
She thinks
she can punk me, huh?
(Zapan grunts)
(screaming)
Hugo, run!
(Zapan grunts)
(grunting)
(woman gasps)
(grunts)
(panting)
ANNOUNCER: Next up is
Second League tryouts.
Will the Factory practice team
report to the line?
(crowd cheering)
The winner tonight will
make it one step closer...
to qualifying
for the Champions League.
Well, that is
one tough lineup.
This is gonna be
one heck of a match tonight.
(grunting)
That's no Factory team.
What?
These two punks in the back...
there are bounty markers
on them.
And the other guys,
they are Hunter-Warriors.
(gasps)
ANNOUNCER: And here comes
tonight's one new prospect.
Okay, then, folks,
give it up for Alita!
Hugo brought her right to us.
What'd you promise him?
Hmm.
I'm sending him to Zalem,
of course.
(chuckles)
(crowd cheering)
Alita! Alita!
Hey.
ANNOUNCER: Since there is
only one new prospect...
What's up?
...there will be no teams.
The name of the game
is Cut-throat.
Go easy on me, guys.
Sure, kid.
No worries.
(comm chimes)
IDO: Alita!
What are you doing?
It's a setup.
You gotta get outta there.
They're gonna kill you!
Which ones?
All of them!
ANNOUNCER:
Players, 10-second warning.
(scoffs)
Five seconds...
(machine beeps)
The new kid, Alita,
takes possession
right off the snap.
(players grunting)
(screams)
(cheering)
A slow Tuesday night just
got hotter than the playoffs.
(all grunting)
Looks like the fans
have themselves
an underdog darling...
with the face of an angel
and a body built for battle.
(grunts)
(crowd exclaims)
Maybe a little Motorball
will break out
in the middle of this fight.
Oh, crap.
(grunts)
(crowd cheering)
Oh! Looks like it's
"No rules Tuesday"
out there, folks.
(weapon whirring)
Ouch!
You know that hurts!
(yells)
(Alita grunting)
Stinger's got Alita
in a lot of trouble.
(yells)
She must've said something
in the locker room
that these guys did not like.
(grunts)
Number 99...
Alita!
(panting) Ali, it's me.
I've got a big problem.
Hugo, this is not a good time.
HUGO: He's trying to kill me.
Who's trying to kill you?
Zapan, the Hunter-Warrior.
He killed Tanji.
ALITA: What do you mean?
HUGO: Now, he's coming for me.
ANNOUNCER:
Not sure our Battle Angel
can get out of this one.
Oh, shit. Here he comes!
ALITA: Where are you?
HUGO: I'm headed
to the old church.
Okay. I'm coming.
ANNOUNCER: I can't believe it!
Incredible!
I've never seen
anything like this.
(grunting)
(screaming)
Hey, I'm almost there.
Got it.
(grunts)
(Alita grunting)
(grunting)
(screaming)
Where are you going, huh?
(groaning)
Looks like your Hugo hasn't
been entirely honest with you.
Is it true?
Ali...
you don't understand.
I never killed anyone.
We only jacked parts.
We paralyzed them
and stripped them, that's all.
I needed the money for Zalem.
Step aside
and let me do my job.
(grunts)
Touch him again
and I will kill you.
Interference between
a licensed Hunter-Warrior
and his kill...
is a violation of Factory Law
and the Hunter's Code.
He's mine!
Then make the kill.
Come on, Hunter-Warrior.
Tonight, you become
one of us.
(laughs)
Mm-mmm.
You know, there's no room
for love or mercy
in the Hunter's Code.
Let me make it easier for you.
(gasps)
(gasping)
ALITA: Hugo!
CENTURION:
Deliver the criminal Hugo,
Bounty 9107.
Wanted for the crime
of murder.
You better finish him
before we do!
It's Hunter Law! (laughs)
I have to get you to Ido.
No. Centurions.
If you go back out there
with me alive,
they'll kill us both.
(Hugo groans)
What did you do?
HUGO: I didn't kill that guy.
But what does it matter?
I tore people apart.
People like you, for money.
Where were you tonight?
I went to go
stop the others.
And tell them I quit.
Why?
Because I love you.
(crying)
God, I'm sorry.
(Hugo sobbing)
(comm beeping)
Did you find them?
No.
They're gone.
(softly) You're so cold.
Please don't die.
Please don't.
I'd give him my life
if I could.
Maybe you can.
You have violated Factory Law
and the Hunter's Code
by protecting a wanted felon.
CENTURION: Where is
the criminal Hugo,
Bounty 9107?
Hugo is dead.
I claim the bounty.
Hunter-Warrior 26651.
CENTURION: Claim confirmed.
Ah.
(Zapan laughs)
Yeah, that's a cute trick.
You think this is
gonna work, huh? Hmm?
Give me that.
CENTURION: Violation.
Hunter-Warrior Zapan...
stealing another's bounty
is against Factory Law
and the Hunter's Code.
Thanks.
ZAPAN: My face.
My... My face!
My face!
No!
(Zapan whimpering)
How is he?
This city corrupts
even good people.
He's good.
He's stable.
Chiren's surgical technique
was brilliant.
There's no brain damage.
Vector was running a scam.
If you're born on the ground,
you stay on the ground...
and no amount of money
can change that.
The only one way to get from
the lower world to Zalem...
is to become Final Champion.
You can't buy
your way up there.
But how do you know that
for sure?
I was born there.
I've removed it myself,
the Mark of Zalem.
With our daughter's illness,
Chiren and I were forced
to descend here to Iron City.
And the man responsible
for our exile...
the watcher
behind the eyes...
is Nova.
(gasps)
You had her heart
in your hands...
and you let her live.
I did.
Why?
Because I'm a doctor.
And...
I'm a mother.
And somehow I forgot that.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm out.
Chiren, wait.
Don't you think
it's time you went to Zalem?
(sighs)
I could send you
up there right now.
What I want...
it isn't up there.
(mechanical footsteps
thumping)
(whispering)
I have to do something.
I'll come back for you.
This is my fault.
Don't ever feel sorry
for yourself.
You're the only one
built for this.
Thank you, Father.
Vector!
CENTURION:
Hostile intention detected.
Surrender your weapon.
(grunting)
(powering down)
Security report.
(grunts)
Violation! Violation!
Did you get her?
Security?
You were never going to send
Hugo to Zalem, were you?
VECTOR: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I always keep my promise
to send people up.
Like Dr. Chiren here.
Nova demands body parts
for his experiments.
Especially, the brains
of people he admires.
And that is the only way
anyone ever gets to Zalem.
(breathing raggedly)
(grunts)
(Alita groans)
It took you long enough.
I knew you wouldn't wait
for your fate
to find you, little flea.
(panting)
Get up.
SOLDIER: Defense Ring!
(screaming)
GELDA: Finish the mission.
Destroy Zalem.
(grunting)
(echoing) Destroy Zalem.
I know who my enemy is.
And I know
he's watching us now.
And you're just his slave.
(grunts)
And I'm just
an insignificant girl.
(yells)
(electrical crackling)
(groaning)
Speak.
No. No. No. Wait.
Speak!
What do you want me to say?
I will say anything.
Not you.
Him!
(distorted)
So we finally meet, Alita.
Not your real name, of course.
Nova?
Where are you?
Home. As we speak.
Feet up.
Well, my girl,
you've certainly exceeded
my expectations.
Killing my champion Grewishka.
Most impressive.
And turning a selfish creature
like Chiren.
I didn't see that coming.
So, when you walk out of here,
the Factory won't stop you.
This time.
I don't need
your permission to live.
Others might.
Your Dr. Ido, for example.
And what about Hugo?
He's still alive, isn't he?
We will track him down.
ALITA: Hmm.
I've found the only way
to enjoy immortality...
is to watch others die.
(groans)
You just lost a puppet.
Well, that looks fatal.
No matter.
Vector was getting tiresome.
You've made
the biggest mistake
of your life.
And what's that?
Underestimating who I am.
Then until next time.
Remember.
I see everything.
(comm chimes)
IDO: Alita.
Factory enforcers came
looking for Hugo.
Somehow they knew
he'd been kept alive.
I helped him escape,
but they've sealed the city.
They're going to find him.
Where is he?
He's trying to go up.
Hugo!
Hugo.
Stop.
You have to come down.
We can't stay up here.
There's a bounty on me.
This is the only way.
No, this is dangerous.
We have to get down, now.
If I go back down there,
I'm dead.
No. You have to
listen to me, okay?
I've been right here before.
This is exactly
where Nova wants you.
He's using you to get to me.
Come on,
we have to go back down.
We belong up there, Alita.
We don't belong anywhere
except together.
You'll always be running.
Together.
Come with me.
Please.
We could be free.
(beeping)
Okay.
(chuckles in relief)
No!
(screams)
(screaming)
(both grunting)
Hold on.
I got you.
Okay, okay. Don't move.
Don't move.
I'm gonna lift you up slowly.
(both grunting)
(Alita sobbing)
Thank you...
for saving me.
I love you.
No!
ANNOUNCER: It took her
only a few months...
to rise through the ranks
of the Second League.
And tonight,
she makes her first appearance
in the Champions League.
Where she has a chance
at becoming Final Champion...
and going to Zalem.
(crowd cheering)
(sniffs)
(inhales deeply)
CROWD: (chanting)
Alita! Alita! Alita!
ANNOUNCER: Let's hear it for
the Battle Angel herself...
number 99...
Alita!
(cheering)
CROWD: (chanting)
Alita! Alita! Alita!
(continues chanting)